(Dominoes fall)
(دومينوز تتساقط)
(Toy car)
(سيارة لعبة)
(Ball rolls)
(كرة تتدحرج)
(Music: "This Too Shall Pass")
(موسيقى: This Too Shall Pass)
(Singing)
(غناء)
You know you can't keep letting it get you down,
أنت تعلم أنك لا تسطيع الاستمرار بالسماح لها بإحباطك،
and you can't keep dragging that dead weight around.
ولا يمكنك الاستمرار بجر ذلك الوزن الثقيل.
If there ain't all that much to lug around
إذا لم يكن هناك ما يكبحك
better run like hell when you hit the ground
يجدر بك الجري بسرعة عند وصولك الأرض
When the morning comes
عندما يأتي الصباح
You can't stop these kids from dancing,
لا يمكنك إيقاف هؤلاء الأطفال من الرقص،
but why would you want to,
ولكن لم قد ترغب بذلك،
especially when you're already getting yours?
خصوصًا عندما تحصل على حصتك؟
(Xylophone)
(سيليفون)
(Singing) 'Cause if your mind don't move and your knees don't bend,
(غناء) لأنه إذا لم تتحرك روحك وركبك بقيت ثابتة
well don't go blaming the kids again.
حسنًا لا تلم أولئك الأطفال مجددًا.
(Xylophone)
(ٍسيليفون)
(Singing) When the morning comes
(غناء) عندما يأتي الصباح
When the morning comes
عندما يأتي الصباح
(Xylophone)
(سيليفون)
(Singing) Let it go,
(غناء) لا تبالي
this too shall pass
هذا أيضًا سيمضي
Let it go,
لا تبالي
You know you can't keep letting it get you down,
أنت تعلم أنك لا تستطيع الاستمرار بالسماح لها بإحباطك
you can't keep letting it get you down --
لا يمكنك الاستمرار بالسماح لها بإحباطك
this too shall pass
هذا أيضًا سيمضي
If there ain't all that much to lug around,
إذا لم يكن هناك ما يكبحك،
you can't keep letting it get you down --
لا يمكنك الاستمرار السماح لها بإحباطك
this too shall pass
هذا أيضًا سيمضي
When the morning comes --
عندما يأتي الصباح
you can't keep letting it get you down,
لا يمكنك الاستمرار بالسماح لها بإحباطك
no you can't keep letting it
لا لا يمكنك السماح لها
When the morning comes --
عندما يأتي الصباح
you can't keep letting it get you down,
لا يمكنك الاستمرار بالسماح لها بإحباطك،
no you can't keep letting it
لا لا يمكنك السماح لها
When the morning comes --
عندما يأتي الصباح
you can't keep letting it get you down,
لا يمكنك الاستمرار بالسماح لها بإحباطك،
no you can't keep letting it
لا لا يمكنك السماح لها
When the morning comes --
عندما يأتي الصباح
you can't keep letting it get you down,
لا يمكنك الاستمرار بالسماح لها بإحباطك،
no you can't keep letting it
لا لا يمكنك السماح لها
When the morning comes
عندما يأتي الصباح
(Paint guns fire)
(إطلاق بنادق طلاء)
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Damian Kulash: Thank you, thanks very much.
داميان كولاش: شكرًا لكم، شكرًا جزيلًا لكم.
We are OK Go,
نحن فرقة "OK Go"،
and we've been together as a band since 1998.
ونحن معًا منذ 1998.
But in the last decade,
ولكن في العقد الأخير،
we've become known as much for the elaborate music videos,
أصبحنا مشهورين بالمقاطع الموسيقية المفصلة،
like the one we just saw,
كالذي رأيناه الآن،
as for the songs they accompany.
ومع الأغاني المرافقة لها.
So we will play along with another one of those in a few minutes,
سنقوم بعرض واحد آخر خلال دقائق،
but in the meantime,
ولكن في غضون ذلك،
we want to address this question that we get asked all the time
نود أن نتحدث عن السؤال الذي تُسأل طوال الوقت
but we've really never come up with an adequate answer for it,
ولكن لم نستطع أبدًا استحضار إجابة مناسبة له،
and that is, how do we think of those ideas?
والذي هو كيف نأتي بتلك الأفكار؟
The videos are not all Rube Goldberg machines, by the way.
بالمناسبة، الفيديوهات ليست كلها آله روب غلودبيرك.
Last year we did a dance in zero gravity,
السنة الفائتة قمنا برقصة أثناء انعدام الجاذبية،
out of thousands of musical instruments in the desert,
مكون من الالاف من الأدوات الموسيقية في الصحراء،
and then played them by stunt driving a car through them.
وقمنا بالعزف عليها عبر القيادة بتهور خلالها.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
For one of the videos,
في أحد الفيديوهات،
we choreographed hundreds of people with umbrellas
قمنا بتصميم رقصة باستخدام المئات من الناس مع مظلات
in an abandoned parking lot outside Tokyo,
في موقف مهجور للسيارات خارج طوكيو،
and then filmed them from a drone a half a mile in the air.
وصورناهم باستخدام طائرات بدون طيار عن بعد نصف ميل في الهواء.
So it's all of these ideas that people are curious about,
لذا كل هذه الأفكار التي تجعل الناس فضوليين،
and the reason we've had so much trouble describing how we think of these ideas
والسبب الذي جعلنا نواجه صعوبة في وصف كيفية تفكيرنا بتلك الأفكار
is that it doesn't really feel like we think of them at all.
هو أننا لا نشعر حقيقة أننا نفكر بها.
It feels like we find them.
يبدو كأننا نجدها.
And by way of explanation --
وللتفسير،
well, I have a compulsive habit.
حسنًا أنا لدي عادة لا أستطيع مقاومتها.
I play parallax and perspective games with my eyes pretty much all the time,
أنا ألعب العاب التزيح بعيني (تغير مكان الشيئ ظاهريًا مع تغيرمكان الرؤية)،
and it's something I've been doing since I was a teenager.
وأنا أفعل هذا الشيئ منذ كنت مراهقًا.
And I think the big contributing factor may have been
وأطن أن أهم عامل أدى لذلك هو
that this is how I decorated my high school bedroom.
أنه هكذا زينت غرفتي في الثانوية العامة.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
And being a teenager,
وأثناء مراهقتي،
what I did in there, of course, was just talk on the phone
ما كنت أفعله، بالطبع، هو التحدث على الهاتف
for staggering amounts of time.
لأوقات كثيرة.
So I was in this visual maelstrom
لذا كنت في هذه العاصفة البصرية
just pretty much usually sitting in one place,
فقط أجلس في مكان واحد،
and I guess just the overload in general --
وأعتقد أن زيادة الحمل هذه
my brain kind of tried to make sense of it, and I would --
دفعت دماغي لمحاولة استخراج منطق منه، وكنت أفكر
If I could move my head off to one side a little bit,
أذا قمت بإمالة رأسي لأحد الجوانب قليلًا،
the edge of the desk would line up just perfectly
فإن حافة الدرج ستلائم تمامًا
with that poster on the opposite wall;
مع الملصق على الجدار المقابل،
or if I put my thumb out,
أو إذا رفعت إبهامي,
I could close first my left eye and then my right,
وأغلقت عيني اليسار ثم اليمين
and my thumb would bounce back and forth
فإن إبهامي سينتقل ذهابًا وإيابا
between Jimi Hendrix's left eye and his right.
بين عيني جيمي هيندريكس.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
It was not a conscious thing, of course,
لم يكن أمرًا شعوريًا بالطبع،
this is just kind of the equivalent of doodling while you're talking,
إنه يشبه عندما تقوم برسم أنماط أثناء التحدث.
and it's still something I do all the time.
وهو شيئ ما زلت أفعله طوال الوقت.
This is my wife, Kristin --
هذه زوجتي، كريستين،
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Yeah!
أجل!
Woo!
وو!
And it's not uncommon that we are out at dinner,
وليس أمرًا غريبًا أننا نكون خارجين للعشاء،
and in the middle of a great conversation she'll just stop mid-sentence,
وفي أثناء محادثة رائعة تتوقف زوجتي بمنتصف جملة،
and when she stops is when I realize that I'm the one who's acting weird
وعندما تتوقف أدرك أنني كنت أتصرف بغرابة
because I'm like bobbing and weaving.
لأني أكون أتمايل.
And what I'm trying to do is get that ficus back there
وما أكون أفعله هو أني أحاول أن أجعل شجرة التين التي في الخلفية
to stick out of her head like a ponytail.
تبرز من رأسها كربطة ذيل الحصان.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
The point of telling you all this is that --
الفكرة من إخباركم بهذا،
for me this is what it feels like to have an idea.
هو أنه بالنسبة لي هكذا أحصل على الأفكار.
It's like they're made of these disparate parts,
أنه يبدو أن الأفكار مصنوعة من تلك الأجزاء المنفصلة،
these disparate chunks sort of floating out there.
تلك القطع المنفصلة تطفو خارجًا.
And if you're receptive and you're observant,
وإذا كنت متفتحًا وكنت ملاحظًا،
and crucially, if you're in exactly the right place,
وبالتأكيد، إذا كنت في المكان الصحيح،
you can get them to just line up.
تستطيع جعلهم يترتبون.
So if you get used to --
لذا إذا اعتدت على،
if it's your job to think of ideas this way,
إذا كانت وظيفتك هي التفكير بهذه الطريقة،
they'll start beckoning to you
فإنها سبدأ بالبروز أمامك
the way that Jimi's eyes beckoned from that poster,
كبروز عيني جيمي من الملصق،
or the ficus beckons from behind Kristin's head.
أو بروز الشجيرة خلف شعر كريستسن.
Writing music feels like that process just over and over again,
كتابة الموسيقى يشبه تلك حدوث تلك العملية مرارًا وتكرارًا،
like you've got a bunch of sounds or a groove or a chord progression
الأمر أشبه بامتلاكك مجموعة من الأصوات أو حفرة أو نغم موسيقي
and you're just looking for that thing on the other side,
وأنت فقط تبحث عن ذلك الشيئ في الجهة المقابلة،
that little chunk over there, that puzzle piece that clicks right in.
تلك القطعة، تلك القطعة من الأحجية التي تملأ المكان.
And when it does click,
وعندما توضع تلك القطعة،
it doesn't feel like you thought up that puzzle piece,
لا يبدو أنك فكرت بتلك القطعة،
it feels like you found it --
إنما يبدو أنك وجدتها،
like it was a set of relationships that you unlocked.
كأن هنالك علاقة قمتَ باكتشافها.
But with the videos in particular,
ولكن مع الفيديوهات على وجه الخصوص،
we're usually looking for this specific feeling
نحن نبحث عن ذلك الشعور الخاص
which is wonder.
شعور العَجَب.
And there's always a component of surprise to wonder,
وهناك دائمًا مكون من المفاجئة،
so we're not just looking for good ideas,
لذا نحن لا نبحث فقط عن أفكار جيدة،
we're looking for good ideas that surprise us in some way.
نحن نبحث عن أفكار جيدة تفاجئنا بطريقة ما.
And this causes something of a problem,
وهذا يسبب مشكلة بعض الشيئ،
because ...
لأنه ...
the process that we all use to make stuff,
العملية التي نستخدمها لصناعة الأشياء،
it actually has a very strong bias against surprising ideas.
لديها بعض الانحياز ضد الأفكار المفاجئة.
The process I'm talking about is the one you all know --
العملية التي أتحدث عنها هي التي تعرفونها كلكم،
we all do it all the time.
نحن نفعلها دائمًا.
You think of an idea.
أنت تفكر بفكرة.
You just sit and think of your brilliant idea
أنت فقط تجلس وتفكر بفكرتك المذهلة
and then you come up with a plan
وبعدها تأتي بخطة
for how you're going to make that idea happen.
لكيفية تنفيذ الفكرة.
And then with that plan in mind,
وبعدها وبوجود الخطة في دماغك،
you go back and double-check your original idea
تعود لتتأكد من فكرتك مرة أخرى
and maybe revise it,
ومراجعتها ربما،
and then bouncing back and forth between the idea and the plan,
وبعدها التأرجح ذهابًا وإيابًا بين الفكرة والخطة،
the plan and the idea,
الخطة والفكرة،
eventually you come up with a truly great plan.
وفي النهاية تأتي بخطة رائعة.
And then once you have that, and only then,
وبعدها ، وفقط بعدها،
do you go out and you execute.
تبدأ بالتنفيذ.
And this is like --
وهذا يشبه،
this is sort of a flawless system
هذا نوعًا ما نظام بلا عيوب
in terms of maximizing your resources,
من حيث استخدام مواردك للحد الأقصى،
because this -- super cheap.
لأن هذا رخيص جدًا.
Thinking usually costs very little,
التفكير عادًة يكلف قليلًا،
but this is really expensive most of the time,
ولكن هذا مكلف كثيرًا غالبًا،
so by the time you get there,
وبحلول وقت وصولك هناك،
you want to make sure you're super prepared
تود أن تكون مستعدًا تمامًأ
and you can squeeze every last drop out of what you've got.
ويمكنك استخراج حتى آخر نقطة مما تملك.
But there are problems with this,
ولكن هناك بعض المشاكل في هذا،
and math will help us reveal the biggest one.
والحساب سيساعدنا في الكشف عن واحدة.
Go back to that video that we just showed you.
بالعودة إلى ذلك الفيديو الذي عرضناه للتو،
That Rube Goldberg machine,
آلة روب غلودبيرغ تلك،
it had about 130 interactions in it.
فيها حوالي 130 عنصر متداخل.
That was 130 things
تلك الـ 130 عنصر
that we had to have go according to our plan.
التي كان لزامًا علينا جعلها تعمل وفقًا لخطتنا.
So let's assume that we want to make a new video now,
لذا لنفرض أننا نريد عمل فيديو جديد الآن،
similarly complex -- 130 moving parts.
بنفس التعقيد، 130 جزء متحرك.
If we're really good planners in that system,
إذا كنا مخططين جيدين لذلك النظام،
it seems like maybe we could be good enough
يبدو أننا يمكن أن نكون جيدين كفاية
to get every part of that system to be 90 percent reliable.
حتى نستطيع جعل كل جزء من ذلك النظام فعال بنسبة 90 بالمئة.
90 percent sounds good, right?
90 بالمئة تبدو جيدة، صحيح؟
Well, it's not.
حسنًا، إنها ليست كذلك.
It's terrible actually. The numbers say so.
إنها سيئة في الحقيقة. الأرقام تقول هذا.
The chance of getting all 130 things to not fail at the same time
إن فرصة عدم وقوع جميع الأجزاء دفعة واحدة
is .9 for 90 percent to the 130th power.
هي0.9 مرفوعة للقوة 130.
So calculate that out and you get ...
وبحساب الرقم نحصل على...
(Ding)
(رنّة)
.000001,
0.000001،
which is one ten-thousandth of one percent,
والذي هو واحد في العشرة آلاف من الواحد بالمئة،
so your chance for success is literally one in a million.
لذا فرص النجاح هي حرفيًا واحد في المليون.
(Whistle)
(تصفير)
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
I mean that's not a gamble I want to take,
أعني هذه ليس حتى مغامرة حتى نخوضها،
so let's ratchet up that reliability to 99 percent.
حسنًا لنرفع تلك النسبة إلى 99 بالمئة.
.99 to the 130th power is ...
0.99 مرفوعة للقوة 130 هو...
(Ding)
(رنّة)
.27 -- 27 percent.
0.27، 27 بالمئة.
Significantly less daunting --
نسبة الشك قلت بشكل واضح،
like this might even be usable.
كأن هذا أصبح قابل للتطبيق.
But really think about that.
ولكن حقيقة فكروا بهذا.
How many parts of your lives are 99 percent reliable?
كم جزء من حياتكم يمكنكم الاعتماد عليه بنسبة 99 بالمئة؟
And could you really get 130 of them all in one place at once?
وهل تستطيعون جعل 130 منها في المكان الصحيح مرة واحدة؟
And if you really could,
وحتى إذا استطعتم،
doesn't it seem like you deserve to succeed?
ألا يبدو أنكم تستحقون النجاح؟
Like that is --
كأن
that thing is going to work, right?
هذا الشيئ سيحقق المطلوب، صحيح؟
But no, it actually fails three times more often than it succeeds.
لكن لا، إن نسب فشله هي ثلاث مرات أكبر من نسب نجاحه.
So the upshot of all this
والخلاصة من كل هذا هي
is that if your project is pretty complex --
إن كان مشروعكم معقدًا،
like, you know, every ambitious project is --
كأي مشروع طامح، كما تعلمون،
if you've got a lot of moving parts,
إذا كان فيه العديد من القطع المتحركة،
that have already demonstrably proven that they're 100 percent reliable.
التي أثبتت فاعليتها بنسبة 100 بالمئة.
So now go back to me sitting with my thumb in the air
والآن بالعودة لي ولأصبعي المعلق في الهواء
trying to line up something surprising.
في محاولة إيجاد شيئ مفاجئ.
If the only things I'm allowed to consider in the first place
إذا كان الشيئ الوحيد المسموح لي بالتفكير به
are ideas that have already been done over and over and over again,
هو الأفكار التي استخدمت مرارًا وتكرارًا،
I am screwed.
فقد قضي علي.
However, there are ways around this,
ومع ذلك، فهناك طرق لتجنب هذا،
because we all know that there are tons of untried ideas still out there,
لأننا نعلم أن هناك الأطنان من الأفكار غير المستخدمة،
and plenty of them will turn out to be every bit as reliable as we need,
والكثير منها ستكون كافية تمامًا لتحقيق رغبتنا،
it's just that we don't yet know they are reliable
إننا فقط لا نعلم أنها موثوقة
when we are at this planning phase.
في أثناء مرحلة التخطيط.
So what we do is we try to identify some place
لذا ما نجاول فعله هو محاولة تحديد مكان
where there might just be a ton of those untried ideas.
يحوي العديد من تلك الأفكار غير المستخدمة.
We try to find a sandbox
نحاول إيجاد صندوق رمل
and then we gamble a whole bunch of our resources
وبعدها نغامر بكمية كبيرة من ميزانيتنا
on getting in that sandbox and playing.
في محاولة اللعب بصندوق الرمل ذلك.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
Because we have to trust that it's the process in the sandbox
لأنه يجب علينا أن نؤمن أنه داخل صندوق الرمل
that will reveal to us which ideas are not only surprising,
توجد فكرة ليست مفاجئة فحسب،
but surprisingly reliable.
ولكن موثوقة بشكل مفاجئ.
So some of the sandboxes that we've started videos with.
و بعض الصناديق التي بدأنا بها فيديوهاتنا.
Let's play with optical illusions.
لنلعب بالخداع البصري.
Let's try to dance on moving surfaces.
لنحاول الرقص على سطح متحرك.
Let's try to make toast with a laser cutter.
لنحاول صنع خبزًا محمصًا باستخدام قاطع ليزر.
Or let's do something in one of those zero-gravity airplanes.
أو لنفعل شيئا بأحد تلك الطائرات الخالية من الجاذبية.
But then instead of actually trying to sit there
وبدلًا من محاولة الجلوس
and think out what that something is,
والتفكير بذلك الشيئ،
we spent a full third of our budget getting in an actual Vomit Comet
أنفقنا ثلث ميزانيتنا في تجربة (Vomit comet)
and bouncing off the walls for a week.
والتأرجح على الجدران لأسبوع.
So this may seem to you like testing,
وقد يبدو هذا تجريبًا بالنسبة لكم،
but it really isn't,
ولكن الأمر ليس كذلك،
because at this point we don't yet know what our idea is,
لأننا في تلك المرحلة لم نكن وجدنا فكرتنا بعد،
we don't have a plan to be testing.
ولا يوجد لدينا خطة لنجربها.
So we're just --
لذا نحن فقط،
we're just playing,
نحن فقط نلعب.
we're just trying everything we can think of,
نحن نجرب كل شيئ يمككنا التفكير فيه،
because we need to get this idea space filled up with a chaos
لأننا نحتاج لملئ فراغ هذه الفكرة بالفوضى
like the one in my high school bedroom.
كالموجودة في غرفتي.
Because then, if we can do the bob and weave thing,
لأننا عندها، إذا استطعنا إيجاد شيئ ما،
if we can put our thumbs up and get just a few things to line up --
إذا استطعنا وضع إبهامنا وجعل بعض الأشياء تتسق،
(Ding)
(رنّة)
chances are no one else has ever made those same things line up before.
فإن النتيجة هي الإتيان بشيئ لم يُسبق من قبل.
And when we're done with that project,
وعندما ننتهي من ذلك المشروع،
people will ask us again how we thought of that idea,
فإن الناس سيسألوننا مرة أخرى كيف فكرتم بذلك،
and we'll be stumped, because from our perspective,
ونحن نحتار، لأنه من وجهة نظرنا،
it doesn't feel like we thought of it at all,
لا نشعر أننا فكرنا في الموضوع،
it just feels like we found it.
نحن نشعر كأننا وجدناه.
So we'll play another video for you now and the song along with it.
سنقوم الآن بعرض فيديو آخر لكم وأغنية معه.
This is for the song "The One Moment,"
هذا لأجل الأغنية" The one moment"
and for this one, the sandbox was ballistics and math.
ولأجل هذه الأغنية، كان صندوق الرمل المقذوفات والحساب.
So I spent a full month putting together a giant spreadsheet for this.
إذ أمضيت شهرًا كاملًا في وضع مجسم ضخم مقسم لأجل هذه الأغنية.
It was like my playspace was 400 lines long
إذ كانت مساحته هي 400 عمود
and 25 columns wide --
و25 صف
which I presume that if anybody is going to understand that, it's this crowd.
والذي أفترض أنه إذا كان أحد سيفهم ما قلت، فإنه سيكون هذا الحشد.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
Nothing is better than a giant spreadsheet, right?
لا شيئ أجمل من مجسم ضخم، أليس كذلك؟
Well, thank you everyone, very much.
حسنًا شكرًا لكم جميعًا.
We are OK Go,
نحن "OK Go"،
and this is called "The One Moment."
وهذه "The One Moment".
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
[The One Moment]
[The One Moment]
(Explosions)
(انفجار)
[What you just saw was real
[ما شاهدتموه كان حقيقيًا
and it took 4.2 seconds]
وقد استغرق 4.2 ثانية]
(Video) Let me know when it's safe.
(فيديو)
(Percussion)
(إيقاع)
[Here's the same moment ...
[هذه نفس اللحظة
slowed down.]
بسرعة أبطأ.]
(Music)
(موسيقى)
(Guitar)
(غيتار)
(Singing) You're right,
(غناء) إنك على حق،
there's nothing more lovely,
لا يوجد ما هو أكثر جمالًا،
there's nothing more profound
لا يوجد ما هو أكثر عمقًا
than the certainty,
من الوثوق،
than the certainty that all of this will end
من الوثوق بأن كل هذا سينتهي
That all of this will end
بأن كل هذا سينتهي
So open your arms to me,
لذا افتح لي ذراعيك
open your arms to me
افتح لي ذراعيك
And this will be the one moment that matters,
وهذه سوف تكون اللحظة الوحيدة المهمة،
and this will be the one thing we remember,
وهذا سوف يكون الشيئ الوحيد الذي نتذكره،
the reason to have been here,
وهذا سيكون سبب وجودنا هنا،
and this will be the one moment that matters --
وهذه سوف تكون اللحظة الوحيدة المهمة،
Oh ...
اوه
(Guitar)
(غيتار)
(Singing) So while the mud reclaims our footprints,
(غناء) وبينما يزيل الطين آثار أقدامنا،
and while our bones keep looking back
وبينما تنظر عظامنا للخلف
at the overgrowth that's swallowing the path --
إلى زيادة النمو التي تبتلع الطريق،
but for the grace of God go we,
ولكن بحق الله دعنا نمضي،
but for the grace of God go we
ولكن بحق الله دعنا نمضي
But for the grace of time and chance and entropy's cruel hands --
ولكن بحق الزمن والصدفة والكون القاسي
So open your arms to me,
لذا افتح لي ذراعيك،
open your arms to me
افتح لي ذراعيك
And this will be the one moment that matters,
وهذه سوف تكون اللحظة الوحيدة المهمة،
and this will be the one thing we remember,
وهذا سوف يكون الشيئ الوحيد الذي نتذكره،
the reason to have been here,
وهذا سيكون سبب وجودنا هنا،
and this will be the one moment that matters
وهذه سوف تكون اللحظة الوحيدة المهمة
Oh ...
اوه
So won't you stay here with me
لذا لماذا لا تبقى هنا معي
and we'll build 'til we've blistered our hands
وسوف نبني حتى تتقرح أيدينا
So won't you stay here with me and we'll build us some temples,
لذا لما لا تبقى معي وسنبني لنا بعض المعابد،
build us some castles,
نبني لنا بعض القلاع،
build us some monuments
نبني لنا بعض اللحظات
and burn them all right down
ونقوم بإحراقها جميعًا
(Music)
(موسيقى)
(Singing) So open your arms to me
(غناء) لذا افتح لي ذراعيك
And this will be the one moment that matters,
وهذه سوف تكون اللحظة الوحيدة المهمة،
and this will be the reason to have been here,
وهذا سيكون سبب وجودنا هنا،
the one thing we remember,
وهذا سيكون الشيئ الوحيد الذي نتذكره،
and this will be the one moment that matters
وهذه سوف تكون اللحظة الوحيدة المهمة،
So won't you stay here with me,
لذا لماذا لا تبقى هنا معي،
we'll build 'til we blister our hands
وسنبني حتى تتقرح أيدينا
And this will be the one moment that matters --
وهذه سوف تكون اللحظة الوحيدة المهمة،
So won't you stay here with me and build us some temples --
لذا لما لا تبقى معي وسنبني لنا بعض المعابد
This will be the one moment that matters --
هذه ستكون اللحظة الوحيدة المهمة
Build us some temples --
نبني لنا بعض المعابد
The one moment that matters --
اللحظة الوحيدة المهمة
Build us some monuments --
نبني لنا بعض الآثار
Build us some temples --
نبني لنا بعض المعابد
The one moment that matters.
اللحظة الوحيدة المهمة
Build us some monuments --
نبني لنا بعض الآثار
The one moment that matters, oh
اللحظة الوحيدة المهمة، اوه
(Guitar)
(غيتار)
(Applause)
(تصفيق)